<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Page from Heath Snoek</title>
    <link>https://heathsnoek.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Page from Heath Snoek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 14:24:39 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://heathsnoek.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Uks Most Hated Sales Trainer</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/salesandmarketing/uks-most-hated-sales-trainer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 14:24:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/salesandmarketing/uks-most-hated-sales-trainer/</guid>
      <description>UK&#39;s most hated sales trainer  How to get out of voicemail purgatory   Benjamin Dennehy is the UK&#39;s most hated sales trainer. I came first across this guy on the Mike Winnet podcast / YouTube channel (who indecently puts out the funniest take-downs of online &#39;success&#39; scammers). He is a very down-to-earth sales trainer with a unique perspective on how to be the best salesperson you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Go Template to Iterate Through a Map</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/code/golang/how-to-use-go-template-to-iterate-through-a-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 05:57:12 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/code/golang/how-to-use-go-template-to-iterate-through-a-map/</guid>
      <description>How to use Go html/template to iterate through a map   In this example we&#39;ll use Golang&#39;s html/template package and iterate through a map in our html template.   You can check out a working example of this code in the Go Playground.  Let&#39;s say we have the following structs: type Employee struct { FirstName string LastName string Email string } type Content struct { Department string Employees map[string]Employee }  The Content struct is what we want to display in our html template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peak Performance Summary</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/books/peak-performance-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 06:00:43 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/books/peak-performance-summary/</guid>
      <description>Peak performance  Highlights    Cycle between intense concentration and recovery   Mental energy is like physical energy, it is limited   Stress over time equals growth   Multitasking means performing poorly on all tasks   View stress in a positive light   Mindfulness increases creativity and physical performance   Breaks increase creativity   Sleep for better performance   Getting in the zone - flow   Consistency   Using purpose as motivation   Positive self talk    Brad Stulberg and Steve Magness collaborate on Peak Performance, an exploration of the tools and habits from the most successful people today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effortless Greg Mckeown Summary</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/books/effortless-greg-mckeown-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 06:20:56 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/books/effortless-greg-mckeown-summary/</guid>
      <description>Effortless Greg Mckeown summary  Highlights    Keep it simple stupid - perfection is the enemy of good.   Take the first step - create a MVP (minimum viable product).   Clear your head - remove negative emotions, they make it harder to concentrate.   Be present, be positive - remove distractions from other tasks and negative thoughts.   Make it enjoyable, don&#39;t over exert - don&#39;t endure the task, turn it into an enjoyable challenge to overcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Start a Blog</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/how-to-start-a-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 13:36:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/how-to-start-a-blog/</guid>
      <description>References (SEO, Marketing)[https://www.codeinwp.com/blog/starting-a-blog/]
Writing  Write blog posts about specific issues in your industry that people are interested in (right now). Write catchy headlines. Listen to feedback and questions from users. Consider your audience and the actions you want them to take. Speak to your audiences goals, pains and challenges. Define your buyer persona - what matters to them, their pains. Write in a conversational style, don&amp;rsquo;t be too stiff. Write in a style that is effortless to read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effortless Excerpts</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/books/effortless-excerpts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 06:14:26 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/books/effortless-excerpts/</guid>
      <description>There’s an upper limit to how much time and effort we can invest. And the more depleted we get, the more our return on that effort dwindles. The lesson is similar to the one I’d always ascribed to: if you prioritize the most important things first, then there will be room in your life not only for what matters most but also for other things too. But do the reverse, and you’ll get the trivial things done but run out of space for the things that really matter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Risk Warren Buffet</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/risk-warren-buffett/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 16:02:30 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/risk-warren-buffett/</guid>
      <description>Warren Buffet on risk   Volatility does not measure risk.
  Beta is a measure of volatility, it is wrong as a measure of risk.
  Past volatility does not determine the risk of investing.
  He gives the example of a farm that was welling for $2000 an acre. A few years later due to various economic factors the price dropped to $600 an acre. According to Beta a purchase of the property at $600 is riskier than buying that same property years earlier at $2000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seth Godin Welcome to the Revolution</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/salesandmarketing/seth-godin-welcome-to-the-revolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 05:12:09 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/salesandmarketing/seth-godin-welcome-to-the-revolution/</guid>
      <description>We are living through a revolution because of the pandemic. Revolutions destroy the &amp;lsquo;perfect&amp;rsquo; and enable the impossible. We are all living virtually now. &amp;lsquo;Perfect&amp;rsquo; - means you play the game and you&amp;rsquo;re winning well enough to play the game. Telegraph was perfect before the telephone. People dealing with perfect usually say &amp;lsquo;no&amp;rsquo; to the new technology. Yahoo had a chance to buy Google for 10 mil. Management is not the same as leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seth Godin How to Make Sure You Never Get Fired</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/salesandmarketing/seth-godin-how-to-make-sure-you-never-get-fired/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 14:51:28 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/salesandmarketing/seth-godin-how-to-make-sure-you-never-get-fired/</guid>
      <description>Problem in the US used to be over-production from factories.  We needed to find out how to get people to buy lots of stuff. We needed people to be cogs in the system to work for these factories. Public schools were invented to [in part] to fix this. If you fit in, you can become a part of this giant machine.   Art is the opposite of being a compliant cog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seth Godin Marketing Masterclass - Notes</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/salesandmarketing/seth-godin-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 05:46:35 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/salesandmarketing/seth-godin-notes/</guid>
      <description>Marketing Masterclass  Marketing is &amp;lsquo;Work that matters for people who care&amp;rsquo; not spamming. What do we make? We are trying to make a change happen.  Does that mean better? Better is always in the eyes in the customer. Enemy of better is average. Don&amp;rsquo;t yell at everyone about your average product. Minimum viable audience.   Make something better for people who need something better. Seek minimum viable audience, the smallest audience you can live with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Launch an App</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/how-to-launch-an-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 08:34:54 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/how-to-launch-an-app/</guid>
      <description>How to Launch an App Market Research  Find out who your competitors are. How much do they charge / do they use an advertising model? What features do they offer? Have a look at competitor app reviews. Why would users be interested in this app? Unique selling point. How to reach target audience. Best time to launch app.  Competitor research:  Who they are. What are their unique selling points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Psychology of Money - summary</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/books/the-psychology-of-money-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 10:15:29 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/books/the-psychology-of-money-summary/</guid>
      <description>The Psychology of Money Timeless lessons on wealth, greed and happiness My Impressions
You are not so Smart  No one can accurately predict the market. No one can see it happen, only explain it away after it has happened. The economy is not like engineering, physics is guided by laws that we understand and can measure, the economy is guided by people and behaviours which is much harder to predict.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Up on Wall Street - summary</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/books/one-up-on-wallstreet-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 10:13:58 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/books/one-up-on-wallstreet-summary/</guid>
      <description>One Up on Wall Street Summary Balance Sheets  Cash flow is a good indicator of company&amp;rsquo;s prosperity. An increasing cash flow from year to year is an indicator of an improving company. Long-term debt reduction is another sign of prosperity. Compare long-term debt over the years and if it is reducing, that&amp;rsquo;s a good sign. Cash exceeding debt it is very favourable. A company cannot go bankrupt if it has more cash than debt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep_work_excerpts</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/books/deep_work_excerpts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 10:10:22 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/books/deep_work_excerpts/</guid>
      <description>Excerpts
By consolidating his work into intense and uninterrupted pulses, he’s leveraging the following law of productivity: High-Quality Work Produced = (Time Spent) x (Intensity of Focus)
By maximizing his intensity when he works, he maximizes the results he produces per unit of time spent working.
The very best students often studied less than the group of students right below them on the GPA rankings. One of the explanations for this phenomenon turned out to be the formula detailed earlier: The best students understood the role intensity plays in productivity and therefore went out of their way to maximize their concentration—radically</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Work - summary</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/books/deep_work_summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 10:08:50 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/books/deep_work_summary/</guid>
      <description>Deep Work Review Deep work can be summed up into an oversimplified equation:
High-Quality Work Produced = (Time Spent) * (Intensity of Focus) My Main take-aways Task switching is the enemy of deep work  This includes pop-up notifications, over-heard conversations, briefly checking emails. Task switching leaves task residue. Switch from task A to task B and there will be some residue of task A in your brain occupying space and reducing the depth of your work.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
