<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Page from Heath Snoek</title>
    <link>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Page from Heath Snoek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 10:00:51 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://heathsnoek.me/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Start a Blog</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/how-to-start-a-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 13:36:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/how-to-start-a-blog/</guid>
      <description>References (SEO, Marketing)[https://www.codeinwp.com/blog/starting-a-blog/]
Writing  Write blog posts about specific issues in your industry that people are interested in (right now). Write catchy headlines. Listen to feedback and questions from users. Consider your audience and the actions you want them to take. Speak to your audiences goals, pains and challenges. Define your buyer persona - what matters to them, their pains. Write in a conversational style, don&amp;rsquo;t be too stiff. Write in a style that is effortless to read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Risk Warren Buffet</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/risk-warren-buffett/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 16:02:30 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/risk-warren-buffett/</guid>
      <description>Warren Buffet on risk   Volatility does not measure risk.
  Beta is a measure of volatility, it is wrong as a measure of risk.
  Past volatility does not determine the risk of investing.
  He gives the example of a farm that was welling for $2000 an acre. A few years later due to various economic factors the price dropped to $600 an acre. According to Beta a purchase of the property at $600 is riskier than buying that same property years earlier at $2000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seth Godin Welcome to the Revolution</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/seth-godin-welcome-to-the-revolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 05:12:09 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/seth-godin-welcome-to-the-revolution/</guid>
      <description>We are living through a revolution because of the pandemic. Revolutions destroy the &amp;lsquo;perfect&amp;rsquo; and enable the impossible. We are all living virtually now. &amp;lsquo;Perfect&amp;rsquo; - means you play the game and you&amp;rsquo;re winning well enough to play the game. Telegraph was perfect before the telephone. People dealing with perfect usually say &amp;lsquo;no&amp;rsquo; to the new technology. Yahoo had a chance to buy Google for 10 mil. Management is not the same as leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seth Godin How to Make Sure You Never Get Fired</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/seth-godin-how-to-make-sure-you-never-get-fired/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 14:51:28 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/seth-godin-how-to-make-sure-you-never-get-fired/</guid>
      <description>Problem in the US used to be over-production from factories.  We needed to find out how to get people to buy lots of stuff. We needed people to be cogs in the system to work for these factories. Public schools were invented to [in part] to fix this. If you fit in, you can become a part of this giant machine.   Art is the opposite of being a compliant cog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seth Godin Marketing Masterclass - Notes</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/seth-godin-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 05:46:35 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/seth-godin-notes/</guid>
      <description>Marketing Masterclass  Marketing is &amp;lsquo;Work that matters for people who care&amp;rsquo; not spamming. What do we make? We are trying to make a change happen.  Does that mean better? Better is always in the eyes in the customer. Enemy of better is average. Don&amp;rsquo;t yell at everyone about your average product. Minimum viable audience.   Make something better for people who need something better. Seek minimum viable audience, the smallest audience you can live with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Launch an App</title>
      <link>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/how-to-launch-an-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 08:34:54 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heathsnoek.me/posts/how-to-launch-an-app/</guid>
      <description>How to Launch an App Market Research  Find out who your competitors are. How much do they charge / do they use an advertising model? What features do they offer? Have a look at competitor app reviews. Why would users be interested in this app? Unique selling point. How to reach target audience. Best time to launch app.  Competitor research:  Who they are. What are their unique selling points.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
